truefire.com 2010-06-08

# TrueFire FAQ

**What is TrueFire's Privacy Policy?**

TRUEFIRE PRIVACY STATEMENT 

Information Collection and Use  
TrueFire is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties. 

Registration  
No registration is required to view content on the TrueFire website. However, in order to use TrueFire to self-publish, purchase or download content registration is mandatory. Member details collected during registration include email address and acceptance of our Member Agreement. TrueFire sends all new members a verification email to verify intent to join, email address, password and username. 

Sharing  
We do not share personally identifiable information about our members or the performance of their self-published content. We do not share or rent our member’s email addresses.

Unsubscribe/Opt-out  
All TrueFire email communications provide members with an opportunity to unsubscribe (opt-out) at any time by clicking on a link at the bottom of the email. Members may also click on a link at the bottom of the email to view TrueFire's Privacy Policy. Members may also Opt-out by emailing us at help@truefire.com.

Client Data  
TrueFire supports the promotion and distribution of Member’s self-published content by managing their content database and tracking various activities related to their own content and downloads of free or paid content which is self-published by other Members. TrueFire keeps all Members’ content data private and this data is never shared with third parties except when required by law. 

Cookies  
TrueFire uses cookies for the sole purpose of automating the log-in process. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally-identifiable information while on our site.

HTML and Link Detectors  
TrueFire embeds HTML and link detectors in all email transmissions. The detectors track recipients' capability of receiving HTML messages and the aggregate number of HTML messages opened. The detectors also track the links that recipients click on within the email. The detectors do not collect any other information. 

Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Online Security  
Online security is enhanced by our use of firewalls protecting all of the TrueFire servers. The physical servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure facility that only authorized network administrators have access to. This facility provides security 24 hours a day, 365 days a year and protects our servers against power outages by using automated backup power systems. 

Offline Security  
Client information and data is stored in a secure facility within the TrueFire offices. Only TrueFire employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are trained on our security and privacy practices. 

Client Communication  
Clients will receive administrative emails that are related to the operational management of their account, such as monthly statements and electronic invoices. TrueFire also sends emails promoting content and other TrueFire activities. TrueFire does not allow 3rd parties to advertise or otherwise correspond with TrueFire Members. From time-to-time, we may request information from clients via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary. Information requested may include contact and demographic information, as well as opinions about TrueFire. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the service. 

Changes to Privacy Policy  
\- Changes to TrueFire's privacy policy will be posted on the TrueFire website. Changes will automatically be in effect 30 days after they are initially posted. TrueFire will send an email to all Members advising them of any changes and their effective date. 

Contact Us  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or about TrueFire, please contact us directly at: phone (727-898-8866) or email info@truefire.com. You can reach us by postal mail at 290 9th Street North, Suite 200, St Petersburg, FL 33705.
